stubbsandwootton.com 2012-12-04

# Privacy Policy

**Security**

Stubbs & Wootton protects your online order and registration information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than Stubbs & Wootton. The secure mode begins when you initiate your order. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. You can double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser when accessing a secure service. The first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https". Some versions of the browsers and some firewalls don’t permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you’ll be unable to connect to the server so you won’t have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection.

**Privacy** ** **

We respect your privacy and, therefore, Stubbs & Wootton does not sell or rent the personal information you provide to us to any third party. We will not share your personal information with any unaffiliated third party without your consent. 

Stubbs & Wootton may, from time to time, contract with unaffiliated third parties that assist us in providing our products and services to you; assist in maintaining and managing customer information to provide customer and internet services; to take and fulfill orders; to conduct Stubbs & Wootton promotions and surveys; or to more effectively communicate with our customers. These companies are contractually-restricted from using your information in any manner, other than in helping us to provide you with the products and services available on our site. Stubbs & Wootton does not authorize any unaffiliated third party to make any other use of your information. 

We will add you to our mailing list when you supply us with your address. If you do not wish to receive our catalog, please contact us via email, phone, fax or mail. Include your name and address as it was supplied to us, and indicate "Do Not Mail". 

Sometimes we make our mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products and services might interest you. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us via email, phone, fax or mail. Include your name and address as it was supplied to us, and indicate "Do Not Share". Additionally we may disclose your personal information as a result of the sale of the stock of all or substantially all of the assets of Stubbs & Wootton, whether by merger, acquisition, or similar or related transactions or in the event of a liquidation of the assets of the company.

If you have chosen not to receive email or postal mailings from Stubbs & Wootton prior to your participation in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey, you may still receive information from Stubbs & Wootton in connection with such activity if you register for or participate in it. You may also choose not to participate in contests, sweepstakes, promotions or surveys if you do not wish to receive information about Stubbs & Wootton or share your information with Stubbs & Wootton and the other companies sponsoring such activities at any time by contacting us by either email, phone or post mail.

If you reach StubbsandWootton.com from a link on another website or search engine, information about your visit to StubbsandWootton.com may be collected by the provider of the referring website. You are encouraged to review the Privacy & Security Statement of these other websites (or search engines). You can avoid this by entering StubbsandWootton.com directly into the address field of your browser.

**Information Collected** ** **

Stubbs & Wootton values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions. Stubbs & Wootton recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. 

We collect information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, and phone and credit card numbers) that you provide when you place an order, join our mailing list, register with us or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also maintain a record of your product interests and your purchases online and in our stores. 

To serve you better, the information you supply to us is added to our customer database. We will add you to our mailing list. From time to time, you may receive periodic mailings or emails from us about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive such emails or mailings from us, please contact us via email, phone, fax or mail (our numbers and addresses are listed below). You may unsubscribe from our email list directly on the website. Telephone numbers are only used to contact you regarding an order placed with Stubbs & Wootton. They are not used for any promotional purpose(s). 

We may combine information you give us online and in our stores as well as information about your product interests and purchases. In addition, we may combine information you provide with demographic information that is publicly available. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, and to communicate with you by email or postal mail about our products, services, contests and promotions that may be of interest to you.

**Updating or Changing Information** ** **

If at any time you want to update or change your information, simply sign on to StubbsandWootton.com as usual, and click on MY ACCOUNT on the top navigation bar. Once logged in, you will see OPTIONS where you will be able to change any personal information. 

If at any time you would like us to update your personal information or remove you from our email or postal mailing lists, feel free to contact us. Please be sure to include your email address, full name and password.

**Your California Privacy Rights** ** **

Beginning January 1, 2005, under California law, if you are a resident of California, you may make a written request to Stubbs & Wootton about how we have shared your personal customer information with select third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, Stubbs & Wootton will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and address. Please submit a written request to the following address: Customer Service, 502 Palm Street Unit 7 West Palm Beach, 33401. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response.

**Cookies** ** **

We use "cookies" to enhance your experience with our site. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. But to take full advantage of the www.StubbsandWootton.com experience, we recommend that you leave them turned on. However, if you would still like to place an order, simply call us at 1 (877) 478-8227 to place your order by phone.

**Children's Privacy** ** **

Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files. Please note: we may nevertheless maintain a record of that person's name and address in a "do not register" file to avoid subsequent registration by a child under the age of 13.

**Changes to this Statement** ** **

Stubbs & Wootton may update this Privacy & Security Statement from time to time. When we make changes, we will post them here. You may wish to check this section from time to time, because by visiting our website you agree to accept any such changes to these policies. Except as otherwise mentioned herein, the Privacy & Security Statement only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website.

**Contact Us**

By Email: [customerservice@stubbsandwootton.com](mailto:customerservice@stubbsandwootton.com)  
By Phone: 1 (877) 478-8227

By Mail:  
Customer Service   
502 Palm Street Unit 7  
West Palm Beach, 33401

Effective as of December 1st, 2010
